Meet Jitar.
An open-source, distributed runtime
for JavaScript and TypeScript applications.
On the surface, it looks simple.
But inside, it’s doing something powerful.
It manages a full-stack
monolithic application.
Which is loved for its simplicity.
And with good modularity,
it can even scale for big apps and teams.
But there are a few drawbacks.
For example, when the application becomes
too big to deploy effectively, releases are slowed down.
Or, when one module is under heavy load,
the whole app must scale, wasting resources.
Or, when one module fails,
it could take down the whole application.
And this is where Jitar comes in.
It provides the tools to overcome these limitations...
by taking your full-stack
monolithic application.
By configuration,
it splits the application into smaller, independent bundles...
and deploying them across
web browsers and servers.
Jitar handles the communication automatically,
so everything works seamlessly.
This gives your application the power
and flexibility of distributed systems...
exactly when you need it.
It seamlessly integrates frontend
and backend, with safe type sharing.
And it doesn’t lock you into
any framework or library.
But it has more to offer.
It comes with batteries included.
Like, request routing, load balancing,
health monitoring, access control, and more.
Overall, Jitar simplifies developing and
deploying scalable full-stack applications...
and makes you more productive.
It includes everything you need to scale,
at any time, at any place.
Check out jitar.dev for more information.